<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Arabicly Blog</title><description>Comprehensive Online Arabic Education</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Arabicly Blog</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 1.22</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 08:40:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Arabicly: Learn Arabic Online</title><description>Arabicly is a comprehensive online education platform that makes it fun and simple to learn and teach Arabic.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/arabicly-learn-arabic-online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b01399549d2920d514806e2</guid><dc:creator>Tamer</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 09:02:18 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/Screen-Shot-2018-06-01-at-1.03.06-AM.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/Screen-Shot-2018-06-01-at-1.03.06-AM.png" alt="Arabicly: Learn Arabic Online"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Salaamu Alaikum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wanted to learn Arabic, but didn't know where to start?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you a Muslim parent looking for a way to teach your child Arabic?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you a masjid volunteer looking for a structured Arabic cirriculum?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can't tell you how many times I've come across these scenarios within our Muslim communities. This is a common pattern among many communities I've visited and even experienced personally. If you're not a native speaker of Arabic or have access to someone who is and is willing to teach you, learning Arabic can be extremely difficult.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arabic is a beautiful language and the language of the Quran. No one should be deprived of learning it due to a lack of resources, we firmly believe that. So a group of us set out with a goal to make learning Arabic accesible to anyone, fun, and simple, inshaAllah!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="arabicly"&gt;Arabicly&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arabicly is a website available anytime, anywhere for both students and teachers to learn Arabic. It's a new innovative way of teaching which provides a game like experience to keep students actively engaged with fun educational lessons that do not require textbooks. With both students and teachers in mind, we've not only created multiple lessons but have incorporated all the features needed to manage a classroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've been piloting Arabicly within our local masjid and both the kids and teachers have loved it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/Kids-copy.jpg" alt="Arabicly: Learn Arabic Online"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check it out at &lt;a href="https://arabic.ummatna.com"&gt;Learn Arabic&lt;/a&gt; and let us know what you think!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>